Take your height in metres, square it, then divide it by your weight in kilograms.
以米为单位测量你的身高，将其平方，然后用你的体重公斤数除以这个结果。
That's how you calculate your body mass index, or BMI.
这就是计算身体质量指数的方法。
If it's between 18 and 25, your weight is healthy.
如果结果在18到25之间，你的体重就是健康的。
If it's over, it isn't.
如果高于这个范围，就不健康。
So far, so simple.
到目前为止，一切都很简单。
BMI has become a popular metric for people to check their health.
身体质量指数已成为人们检查健康状况的常用指标。
On a population level, data backs this up.
在人口层面上，数据支持这一点。
People with a high BMI are statistically more likely to develop conditions such as hypertension, diabetes, arthritis, and some types of cancer along with other health problems.
统计数据显示，身体质量指数高的人更容易患上高血压、糖尿病、关节炎、某些类型的癌症以及其他健康问题。
Checking BMI could be a way for people to easily assess their health and decide if they need to make any lifestyle changes.
检查身体质量指数可能是人们评估自己健康状况并决定是否需要改变生活方式的一种很容易的方法。
However, BMI does not give the full picture.
然而，身体质量指数并不能反映全貌。
It's known that it's less accurate for some groups of people, such as children, the elderly or athletes.
众所周知，它对某些人群（如儿童、老年人或运动员）的准确性较低。
The measure was devised in the 19th Century by a Belgian mathematician, and this may be why the figures are more accurate for Europeans than other ethnicities.
这个测量方法是在19世纪由一位比利时数学家设计的，这可能解释了为什么它对欧洲人比对其他族裔更准确。
There are also several important factors that it doesn't measure.
还有几个重要因素它没有测量。
Someone who is very active may have significant weight from muscle.
一个非常好动的人可能因肌肉而体重较大。
BMI doesn't differentiate between this or the visceral fat that is linked with negative health outcomes.
身体质量指数无法区分这一点与内脏脂肪，而内脏脂肪与负面的健康结果相关。
It doesn't account for the range of nutrients or the level of cholesterol in someone's diet.
它也不考虑一个人饮食中的营养种类或胆固醇水平。
What this means is that people can have a high BMI and be relatively healthy, while others may have a low BMI but be unhealthy.
这意味着有些人身体质量指数高却相对健康，而另一些人身体质量指数低却不健康。
The simplicity of BMI is attractive, it's also very visible and fits with society's perception of the importance of weight.
身体质量指数的简单性很有吸引力，它也很直观，符合社会对体重重要性的认知。
However, dependence on it as an indication of health can cause stigma.
然而，依赖其作为健康指标可能会造成污名化的问题。
People can feel judged because of their weight.
人们会因为体重而感到被评判。
This sometimes leads people to avoid going to the doctors if they know they're likely to be questioned on it.
这有时会导致人们避免去看医生，如果他们知道可能会被问到体重问题。
While BMI may be a useful measure, experts remind us that it should always be considered alongside other measures, such as blood pressure, blood sugar level, cholesterol level and others.
虽然身体质量指数可能是一个有用的测量指标，但专家提醒我们，它应该始终与其他指标（如血压、血糖水平、胆固醇水平等）一起考虑。